Michael Goodman

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Phone: (731) 412-8301 | Email: Magoody12@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/Michael-Goodman01 https://github.com/MaGoodman12

Introduction

With an inquiring mind and a love for learning, I strive for success in anything I set my hands towards in order to find and share intriguing information in today's ever-changing field of relevant data. I hope to expand my experience and skillset so I may improve the daily lives of those in which I am involved.

Skills

- Excel
- SOL
- PowerBI
- Tableau
- Jupyter
- Python

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Nashville Software School

Nashville, TN

Analytic Internship Certification Course Projects

July 2021 – January 2022

- *will place link to capstone here*
- PowerBI Dashboard
- Tableu Dashboard
- Nashville Parks Geospatial Project
- *will place link to final python project here*

TriStar Centennial Medical Center

Nashville, TN

Nursing Unit Clerk/Secretary

Patient Transport Shift Supervisor

Patient Transporter

October 2020 - Present January 2020 – October 2020 August 2018 – January 2020

- Multiple data systems operations
- Department purchase and resupply
- Team member hiring, training and guideline document creation
- Patient transportation
- Disease disinfection and department upkeep

Nissan North America

Smyrna, TN

Material Handler/Forklift Operator

Mechanical Production Technician

January 2016 – July 2018 August 2014 – January 2016

- Supply transportation and distribution
- Power tool and heavy machine operations
- Vehicle part build and assembly

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Nashville Software School

Nashville, TN

Data Analytics Apprenticeship

July 2021 - January 2022

Volunteer State Community College

Gallatin, TN

Varying courses completed

August 2020